-嘿 -嗨
- Hey. - Hi.
-你在做什么? -我想把沙发搬开
- What are you doing? - I was thinking of moving the couch.
你为什么要那么做?
Why would you want to do that?
那样子我就有好位置可以坐了?
So there'd be a decent place for me to sit?
-瑞秋，你本来就有好位置坐 -你的大腿不算
- Rach, there is a decent place. - And your lap does not count.
-来吧，帮我把它搬开 -不
- Come on, help me move this. - No, no, no.
-你不要 -我不要
- No? - No.
萝希塔不想移开
Rosita does not move.
对不起，萝希塔，它是…?
I'm sorry. Rosita? As in...?
就是“不想动的萝希塔”
As in "Rosita does not move."
它只是一张椅子，它有什么大不了的?
It's just a chair. What's the big deal?
它到浴室跟到厨房的距离是一样的…
It's the exact equal distance from the bathroom to the kitchen...
而且它的角度让你完全看不到史提夫的闪光
...and it's at an angle where you don't get any glare coming off Stevie.
电视机叫史提夫?
Stevie the TV?
-有问题吗? -没有
- Is there a problem? - No.
他又知道什么?
What does he know?
来吧，萝希塔，我们这些辣妹得合作才行
Come on, Rosita. Us chicas gotta stick together.
你这个贱人!
You bitch!
Friends S07E13 萝希塔死了
The One Where Rosita Dies
你知道什么事奇怪吗?
Hey, you know what's weird?
等你们结婚了 你们向别人介绍我的时候
After you guys get married, when you introduce me to people...
…你得说，“这是我大舅子，罗斯”
...you're gonna have to say, "This is my brother-in-law, Ross."
而不是“我的朋友，罗斯”，是“大舅子，罗斯”
Not "my friend, Ross," "brother-in-law, Ross."
很奇怪，对吗?
That's weird, isn't it?
难道我不能说，“这是罗斯”吗?
Couldrt I just say, "This is Ross"?
可以，随你便!
Sure, do whatever you want.
嘿，罗斯?
Hey, Ross?
我看过房地产广告版
I checked the real estate section.
你看这个
Look at this.
看起来好像爸妈的房子
Looks like Mom and Dad's house.
院子里的树，正前方也有根断掉的树枝
Even has a tree with a broken limb out front.
阁楼的窗户…
And the window in the attic...
哦，我的天啊!
Oh, my God!
阁楼的窗户怎么了?
What happened to the window in the attic?
-我不敢相信他们要把它卖掉 -却没有告诉我们
- I can't believe they're selling it. - And they didn't tell us.
阁楼的窗户怎么了?
What happened to the window in the attic?
爸爸吗? 莫妮卡和我刚刚在报纸上看到房子的事
Hello, Dad? Monica and I just saw the house in the paper.
是的，我们吃了一惊
Yes, we're surprised.
你告诉谁了?
Who did you leave a message with?
对不起!
Sorry!
乔伊，真是对不起
Joey, Joey, I'm so sorry.
跟你说过不要动它! 你会什么感觉，如果，我是说
I told you not to move it! How would you feel if, say...
我要搬动你妈妈，好吧…
...I wanted to move your mom, okay...
…你说，“别”，但我还是那样做了…
...and you said, "Don't," and I did it anyway...
…接着她的头掉了?
...and her head fell off?
我会买张新椅子赔你，好吗?
I'll buy you a new one, okay?
我们马上到店里去帮你买一张新椅子
We'll go to the store and get you a new chair right now.
她还尸骨未寒
She's not even cold yet.
萝希塔不希望你继续过你的日子吗?
Wouldrt Rosita have wanted you to move on?
我是说她永远把你的幸福放在第一位
I mean, you know, she did always put your comfort first.
没错
That's true.
-好吧，你准备好了吗? -好了
- Okay, you ready? - Yeah.
我不想史提夫看到她这样
I don't want Stevie to see her like this.
我不敢相信，我们得跟小时候的家说再见
I can't believe we have to say goodbye to the house we grew up in.
天啊，有个陌生人就要搬进我的房间里
Man, some stranger's gonna be in my room.
15年来，他们把你房间弄得跟圣坛差不多
For 15 years they kept it as a shrine to you.
现在一切都该落幕了
It's time the velvet ropes came down.
他们也保留你房间有一阵子
They kept your room a while.
拜托，我搬出来二十分钟后 爸就把我的房间变成健身房
Please! Dad turned my room into a gym 20 minutes after I moved out.
一张日光浴椅跟一堆 《维多利亚的秘密》的目录（女士性感内衣品牌）
I gotta say, a tanning bed and a stack of Victoria's Secret catalogs?
那不是健身房
Not a gym.
-别这样，你知道他们爱你 -就跟他们爱你一样？
- Come on. You know they love you. - As much as they love you?
我没出生前，他们以为她不会生 那不是我的错
They thought she was barren until I was born. It's not my fault.
我讨厌今年
I hate this year.
今年有什么不对的?
What's wrong with this year?
现在已经是二月，我只接到两个按摩客人…
It's February and I've only given two massages...
而且他们给小费都给得很吝啬
...and they were both horrible tippers.
你是指我跟罗斯
That was me and Ross.
哦，没错
Oh, that's right.
如果你需要钱…
If you want some extra cash...
我大学的朋友做电话行销赚了不少钱
...some college friends made good money doing telemarketing.
好主意，你打电话很在行
That's a great idea. You're really good on the phone.
他一定比上次我做的电话行销工作还棒
It'd be better than the last telephone job I had.
或许我不必常常说“打我屁股吧”
I probably won't have to say "spank" as much.
什么?
What?
对，就像你从没打过那种电话似的
Oh, yeah, like you never called.
真的很简单，你只要照着稿子念…
This is very easy. You read from the script...
试着多卖一点碳粉
...and try to sell as much toner as you can.
好吧，我办得到
Okay, I can do that.
对了，我喜欢我的办公室
By the way, I love my office.
-我们为什么不来练习一下? -好吧
- Why don't we do a trial run? - Oh, okay.
好了
All right.
嗨，我是帝国办公室文具公司的菲比
Hi, this is Phoebe from Empire Office Supplies.
-请问总务部经理在吗? -我就是总务部经理
- Can I speak to your supply manager? - I'm the supply manager.
我想跟你谈谈买碳粉的事
I'd like to talk about your toner needs.
我们不需要碳粉
We don't need any.
好吧，抱歉打扰你了，再见
Okay, sorry to bother you. Bye-bye.
你说的对，这真的很容易
Yeah, you're right. This is easy.
好吧，那通电话哪里不对劲呢?
Okay. What was wrong with that call?
好吧
Oh, well, all right.
我没有恶意，但你的态度真的很不好
No offense, but you were kind of rude.
他们永远都会说，他们不需要碳粉，没关系
They always say they don't need toner. That's okay.
不管他们说什么 你都会在稿子里找到标准解答
Whatever they say, you can find the answer to it, here in the script.
我想你准备好要卖碳粉了
So I think you're ready to sell toner.
-你还有问题吗? -没有了
- Do you have any last questions? - No.
等一下，对了，我的确有一个问题
Wait, yes, I do have one question:
什么是碳粉?
What is toner?
乔伊?
Joey?
Joe?
未拆包?
Full bag?
啤酒还是冰的
Beer's still cold.
这里一定发生了很可怕的事
Something terrible must have happened here.
喔，不…
Oh, no, no, no!
史提夫，我没来过这里
Stevie, I was never here.
-爸? -我在这里!
- Dad? - I'm here!
-嗨 -嗨
- Hey. - Hi.
感觉上好像以前你们跑来这里看我工作的时候
Seems like just yesterday you guys used to come out to watch me work.
我们不敢相信你们要卖掉房子
We can't believe you're selling the house.
也该让新的家庭在这里开始他们的新生活了
Time for a new family to start here.
我希望在支票兑现前他们不会发现…
I hope their check clears before they find the crack...
地基有裂痕，天花板的石棉瓦破了
...in the foundation and the asbestos in the ceiling.
我们快把东西拿一拿，离开这里吧
Let's grab our stuff and get the hell out of here.
-抱歉我们不能收藏你们的东西 -没关系
- Sorry we can't store your things. - Oh, it's okay.
我等不及要再看到那些东西了
I can't wait to see everything again.
我不知道这里放了什么
I don't know what's down here.
但阁楼上有六七箱简易烘焙烤箱
But there are six or seven Easy-Bake Ovens in the attic.
我以前最喜欢玩开餐厅的游戏了
I used to love to play restaurant.
但你最爱的还是“吃面粉糊”
Not as much as you loved to play "uncooked batter eater."
你不能要求小孩子等着电灯泡把饼干烤好
You can't expect a child to wait for a light bulb to cook brownies.
我想你的箱子应该都在这里
So I think your boxes are over here.
太棒了
Oh, great.
嘿…
Hey...
这是谁的烟?
...whose cigarettes are these?
我不知道
I don't know.
一定是你妈的
They must be your mother's.
但求求你别去质问她，我来把烟丢掉
But please, please don't ask her. I'll throw these away.
酷啊! 爸，是我的成绩单!
Cool! Dad, my report cards!
嘿，快来看看
Hey, check this out.
数学“优等”，自然“优等”历史“优等”，体育…．
Math, "A." Science, "A." History, "A." Gym...
我的磨石机
My rock polisher!
噢，看，你的旧化妆盒
Oh, look, there's your old makeup kit.
这是小丑盒，小丑盒!
It's a clown kit. Clown kit!
不过白色好像没被碰过
But the white seems to be untouched.
-惨了 -怎么了?
- Uh-oh. - What?
你知道每年春天车库都会淹水吗?
You know how the garage floods every spring?
你要怎么把房子卖掉?
How are you ever gonna sell this place?
我想我不小心把莫妮卡的箱子…
I think I accidentally used Monica's boxes...
来挡水，免得保时捷进了水
...to keep the water away from the Porsche.
哦，不，爸，爸?
Oh, no, Dad. Dad?
搞什么?
What the...
哦，天啊，一切都毁了!
Oh, God. Everything's ruined!
爸，她一定会崩溃的
Dad, she's gonna be crushed.
你该不会是偷偷在抽烟吧?
You don't secretly smoke, do you?
不
No.
那就是你妈在抽烟
So it's just your mother then.
嗨，我是帝国办公室文具公司的菲比
Hi. This is Phoebe from Empire Office Supplies.
请问总务部经理在吗?
Can I speak to your supply manager, please?
厄尔，谢谢
Earl. Thanks.
嗨，厄尔，我是帝国办公室文具公司的菲比
Hi, Earl. This is Phoebe from Empire Office Supplies.
我想跟你谈谈买碳粉的事
I'd like to talk to you about your toner needs.
我不需要碳粉
I don't need any toner.
我知道，但是听了我们的价格 大家都会想买碳粉
I hear what you're saying, but at our prices, everyone needs toner.
我不要
Not me.
能请问你为什么吗?
May I ask why?
你想知道为什么?
You want to know why?
我真的很想
I surely do.
好吧
Okay.
我不需要碳粉…
I don't need any toner...
因为我就要自杀了
...because I'm gonna kill myself.
那是因为你的碳粉用完了吗?
Is that because you're out of toner?
好吧，今天我不需要碳粉，谢谢，再见
Okay, so no toner today. Thanks anyway. Bye-bye.
等一下! 我不能让你挂电话，请你跟我说话
Wait, wait! I can't let you hang up. Just please talk to me.
喔…
Well...
今天我只需要做一件事（今天的任务：自杀）
I only had one thing to do today.
我猜我能把它推迟一下吧
I guess I could push it back.
好吧，你为什么要自杀?
Yeah. Now, why do you want to kill yourself?
十年来，我一直在做…
I've been working for 10 years now at this...
这份没有意义没有前途的工作…
...meaningless, dead-end job...
办公室里的人根本不知道我的存在
...and nobody here even knows that I exist.
钱德?
Chandler?
你说什么?
I'm sorry?
听着…
Look...
我相信他们都知道你的存在
...l'm sure that people know you exist.
是吗? 我在一个小房间工作…
Oh, yeah? I work in a cubicle...
四周都是人
...surrounded by people.
我已经跟你谈了五分钟我要自杀的问题…
I've been talking to you for five minutes now about killing myself...
没有人抬头来看我一眼，等一下
...and no one's even looked up from their desk. Hang on.
嘿，大伙们…
Hey, everybody...
我要自杀了
...l'm gonna kill myself.
回头再跟你们说
I'll get back to you.
没人理我
I got nothing.
等会
Wait.
嘿，马奇
Hey, Marge.
他们不理我
Nothing. Nothing.
好漂亮的椅子
Good chair.
好了，如果有人问起…
Now, if anybody asks...
你的名字就叫萝希塔
...your name is Rosita.
乔伊，我给你买了一张新椅子 商店里最贵的椅子
Come on, Joey. I just bought you a new chair, the most expensive one in the store.
知道我在想什么吗? 给她取名弗朗塞特
You know what I was thinking? We could name her Francette.
弗朗塞特?
Francette?
她是谁，沙发?
What is she, a couch?
可怜的小东西，她是英年早逝
Poor thing. Cut down in her prime.
乔伊，新椅子一小时内就会送来
Joey, the new chair will be here in an hour.
或许我们该把萝希塔搬出去
Maybe we should move Rosita out of here.
开始疗伤过程
Start the healing process.
好吧，我猜你说的对
Yeah, I guess you're right.
也许我要带她去焚化炉
Maybe I'll take her down to the incinerator.
真伤心
It's gonna be so sad.
也有点酷
And kind of cool.
她痊愈了!
She's healed!
-那太奇怪了 -不，一点都不奇怪
- That's weird. - No, it's not weird.
这是奇迹!
It's a miracle!
这不是奇迹，我相信这一定有合理的解释
It's not a miracle. I'm sure there's an explanation.
没错，只要你的心地纯正，奇迹一定会发生
There is. If your heart is pure, wondrous things can happen.
-我不… -你能告诉我怎么回事吗?
- I don't... - Can you tell me how this happened?
-不 -奇迹
- Well, no. - Miracle.
可能有人进来修好它．或者其他什么的
No, you know what, maybe somebody came in here and fixed it. Or something.
天使?
Someone like an angel?
没错，乔伊．椅子天使进来修好了你的椅子
That's right, Joey. The chair angel came in and healed your chair.
从我的椅子上挪开你那不信任的屁股!
Get your non-believer ass out of my chair!
她会了解的，我不是故意的
She'll understand. I didn't do it on purpose.
爸，对她来说那并不重要
Dad, that won't matter to her.
你看，我的箱子完全没事
Look, all my stuff is safe and dry.
她的东西都…
And all her stuff is...
长出新的东西了
...growing new stuff.
就是这样的事
This is the kind of thing...
让她认为你们爱我更胜于爱她
...that makes her think you love me more than her.
天啊，她真的那么认为?
My God. Does she think that?
-你能怪她吗? -我不知道
- Can you blame her? - I don't know.
或许我们在潜意识上是偏爱你的 你是个奇迹
We may have favored you unconsciously. You were a marvel.
-医生说你妈没办法…-我不想听
- The doctors said your mom couldn't... - I don't want to hear it.
-真的吗? -现在不想
- Really? - Well, not right now.
莫妮卡来这里找回忆 该死，我们得给她一些回亿
Monica came here for some memories. Damn it, we'll give her some.
好吧，拿…
Okay, grab...
把空箱子拿过来，我们拿一些我的东西…
Grab some boxes. We'll take stuff from mine...
放在这些箱子里，只要能骗过她就行
...and whatever we can pass off as hers, we'll put in there.
-譬如说这个，这可能是她做的 -没错
- Like, this. She could have made this.- Sure.
还有这个，也可能是她赢的。
And this, she could have won this.
-这可能是她的 -当然
- This could have been hers. - Sure.
-这个是什么? -你的化妆盒?
- Here, what about this? - Your makeup kit?
我感觉好多了
I'd feel better.
我好高兴我能把这张椅子留下来给自己用
I am so psyched I kept this chair for myself.
对，我也是
Yeah. Me too.
-嘿，奇迹椅子怎么样? -很好
- Hey, how's the miracle chair? - Fine.
你知道这张椅子的头垫上还附了喇叭吗?
You know, this thing has speakers in the headrest?
-不，真的吗? -没错
- No, really? - Yeah.
你可以把它跟电视机接在一起还可以听收音机
You can hook it to the TV and you get radio.
我的椅子有自疗的功能
My chair heals itself.
艾尔，你没听我讲话 我是说，你不孤单．好吗
Earl, you're not hearing me. All I'm saying is, you're not alone, all right?
所有人都讨厌他们的同事
Everybody hates the people they work with.
嘿，伙计
Hey, guy.
等一下，那人好像对你挺好
Wait, that sounded like someone being nice to you.
不，只是说句“嘿，伙计”的家伙
No, that's just the "hey, guy" guy.
他对所有人都那样说．他最坏了
He says that to everybody. He's the worst.
我想带他跟我一起死
I'd like to take him with me.
好吧，我们别提办公室的同事了，好吗?
All right. Let's just forget about the people at the office, okay?
一定有人值得你留恋
There's gotta be someone won'th sticking around for.
你的家人跟朋友呢? 或许你有女朋友?
What about family or friends? Maybe a girlfriend?
是啊
Yeah, right.
哦，抱歉，你的男朋友呢?
Oh, sorry. Boyfriend?
-天哪 -不，随便吧，什么都行
- Oh, God. - No, whatever. Anything.
嘿，伙计
Hey, guy.
没错，他应该去死
Yeah, he's gotta go.
好了，我应该…
Okay, I should...
去做我想做的事了
...be getting back to my thing now.
再见
See you.
我还没有说完，你休想挂我电话!
I'm not finished! Don't you dare hang up on me!
新来的女孩真不错
The new girl's good.
嘿，伙计们
Hey, guys.
我定了一些简易烘焙点心．3天内应该准备好了
I just whipped us up some Easy-Bake treats. They should be ready in about three days.
太好了! 听到了吗，罗斯? 3天!
That's a good one! You hear that, Ross? Three days!
-噢，美好的回忆 -好的
- Oh, this'll make a great memory. - Okay.
哪些箱子是我的?
Which boxes are mine?
-你的箱子在这里 -好吧
- These are yours right here. - Okay.
涂色簿
A coloring book.
你喜欢那个玩意
You loved that thing.
你去哪里都会…
You never went anywhere without...
都会带着那本涂色簿
...without that coloring book.
真的吗?
Really?
看起来我老是没办法把颜色涂在线上
Looks like I had trouble staying in the lines.
不
Nuh-uh!
-旧手套? -你以前很喜欢它
- An old glove? - Yeah, you loved that glove.
去哪里都戴着．没有它你哪都不去
You took it every place you went. You never went anyplace without the glove.
哇，你看这个
Wow, look at this.
我不敢相信以前我穿得下这件T恤（暴龙罗斯）
I can't believe I even fit into this shirt.
噢，这是你的
Oh, this is yours.
我不知道它怎么会跑到那里去
I don't know how that got in there.
这不是我的东西
This isn't mine.
嘿，这些不是我的东西
Hey, this isn't my stuff.
罗斯，这些是你的箱子
Ross, these are your boxes.
我的箱子在哪里?
Where are my boxes?
你的箱子…
Your boxes are...
-怎么了? -爸爸?
- What? - Dad?
车库淹水，甜心，你的箱子都进了水，对不起
- The garage flooded, sweetie, and ruined your boxes. I'm sorry.
只有我的箱子进水了?
Just mine?
恐怕是那样的
I'm afraid so.
为什么罗斯的东西都没坏?
Why wasn't Ross' stuff ruined?
如果你说那是“医学奇迹”我要用简易烘焙箱蒸你的头
And if you say the words "medical marvel," I'm going to Easy-Bake your head.
我用你的箱子挡水来保护我的保时捷
I used your boxes to divert water away from the Porsche.
罗斯的东西都没事 但我的回忆都没有了
Ross' stuff is fine, but I have no memories...
只为了你不希望你的汽车底盘碰到水?
...so you could keep the bottom of your car from water?
水里有树叶，泥巴跟杂物
There was also leaves and gook and stuff.
我不敢相信!
I can't believe this!
去他的，我要抽根烟
Screw it. I'm having one.
-嘿，钱德 -嘿
- Hey, Chandler. - Hey.
你要不要试试看一张可以平躺…
How'd you like to sit in a chair that reclines...
有滚轮按摩功能…
...has a rolling massage...
头垫还附了喇叭的椅子?
...and speakers in the headrest?
我试过很多次…
I've tried that so many times...
但他们已经不再让我走进他们店里
...they won't even let me in the store anymore.
如果我说你可以到我家试坐一下呢?
What if I said you could do it in my apartment?
你是说…
Are you telling me...
你买了那张让其他椅子都变成废物的椅子?
...you bought the chair that makes all others obsolete?
那张《椅子杂志》封为“年度最佳椅子”的椅子?
The chair that Sit Magazine called "Chair of the Year"?
我刚刚买了…
I just purchased...
懒男孩E倾斜3000型
...the La-Z-Boy E-Cliner 3000.
噢，那真的是太棒了! 太帅了! 你为什么买下它
Well, that's awesome! That's great! What made you do it?
说来话长，但我弄坏了乔伊的椅子…
It's a long story, but, I broke Joey's chair...
哇…你弄坏了乔伊的椅子?
Whoa, whoa, whoa. You broke Joey's chair?
我以为是我干的 所以我用我的椅子跟它调换
I thought I did, that's why I replaced it with mine.
所以它才会完全没事
That's how it got fixed!
你以为是妖精把它修好的?
You thought that elves came in and fixed it?
不
No.
是天使干的
Angels.
我要把我的椅子拿回来
I'm getting my chair back.
喔，看起来它根本没有自疗功能!
Well, looks like it wasn't healed after all!
我猜这张椅子是我的了
I guess this chair's mine now.
乔伊，你弄坏了我的椅子!
Joey, you broke my chair!
你的椅子?
Your chair?
他以为他把它弄坏了所以他调换了椅子
He thought he broke it, so he switched chairs.
奇迹根本不存在?
So there was no miracle?
没错，乔伊，奇迹不存在
No, Joe. No miracle.
喔，不，这真的是太糟糕了
Oh, no! This is devastating!
我的信念被击垮了 我很高兴这张新椅子能陪我走过这一切
My faith is shaken. I'm glad I have a new chair to get me through this.
不错的尝试．但你不会再拥有那张椅子了
Nice try, but you don't get that chair anymore.
那是我的椅子了．你来坐我的大腿好了
That is my chair now. You can sit on my lap.
不，我收回我的话!
No, I take that back!
我想椅子应该是我的
I think I should get the chair.
-为什么呢? -你弄坏了椅子，你也弄坏了椅子
- How do you figure? - You broke a chair and you broke a chair.
这里没弄坏的椅子的人 只有我
The only one here that hasn't broken a chair is me.
不，不，不．这张椅子哪儿都不能去
No, no, no. This chair's not going anywhere.
-什么逻辑啊? -逻辑…
- Where's the logic in that? - The logic...
…就是我们是两个人…
...is that there are two of us...
…而且我们都强壮到可以把椅子分成两半
...and we are both strong enough to break a chair in half.
那么乔伊弄坏我的椅子，而我一无所获?
So Joey breaks my chair, and I get nothing?
没错
That's right.
你们是谁? 恶徒吗?
What are you guys, like, a gang or something?
没错，是的
Yeah, we are.
我们是眼镜蛇帮
We're the Cobras.
请问厄尔在哪里? 他是总务部经理
Where can I find Earl? He's the supply manager here.
我不认识厄尔
I don't know any Earl.
我就在这里!
I'm right here!
厄尔?
Earl?
我是菲比
I'm Phoebe.
菲比
Phoebe?
卖碳粉的小姐?
The lady who sells toner?
听着，你不能自杀
Look, you can't kill yourself.
我很感激你赶过来…
Look, I really appreciate you coming down...
不，我不能让你那么做
No, I can't let you do it.
-为什么? -因为命运让我今天打电话给你
- Why? - Because, fate made me call you today.
我还以为是碳粉让你打给我的
I thought it was toner.
好好想一想，好吗? 这根本不是我的正职
Think about it, okay? This isn't even my regular job.
我第一天上班就第一个打电话给你
My first day, you're my first call.
其他人可能会挂掉电话，但我不会那么做…
Somebody else may have hung up, but I wouldn't do that...
因为我了解这种事
...because I know about this stuff.
-我妈是自杀的 -真的吗?
- My mom killed herself. - Really?
-她怎么自杀的? -我绝不会教你
- How? - I'm not gonna give you tips.
你看不出来…
Don't you see that this...
这些都是注定的，所以我才会来阻止你自杀?
...all came together so I could stop you from doing this?
-这不是巧合吗? -不，这是命中注定
- Couldrt it just be a coincidence? - No, it's fate.
它看起来不像是命中注定
It doesn't really seem like enough to be fate.
哦，好吧
Oh, well.
好吧，有件事很奇怪
Okay, here's a weird thing.
我妈妈也是总务部经理
My mother was also a supply manager.
事实上我是办公室经理
I'm actually the office manager.
我的天啊! 她也是!
Oh, my God! So was she!
还有这个，好吧
And get this, okay.
你叫厄尔，对吧? 她叫做普厄儿
Your name is Earl, right? Her name was Pearl.
普…厄尔
Puh-Earl.
还有别的证据吗?
Was there anything else?
当然有
Sure.
你是哪里人?
Where're you from?
-费城 -哦，我的天啊，她也是!
- Philadelphia. - Oh, my God, so was she!
我都起鸡皮疙瘩了
I've got goose bumps.
-真的吗? -我穿太多了，而且这里很热
- Really? - I'm wearing layers, and it's warm.
或许这些混蛋不在乎你…
These jerks might not care about you...
但宇宙在乎你，那才是最重要的
...but the universe does, and that says a lot.
你们听到了吗?
Did you hear that?
我不需要你们在乎我…
I don't need you guys to care about me...
因为宇宙在乎我
...because the universe cares!
整个宇宙在乎我!
The whole universe!
我真的希望他们能在乎我一下
I really wish they'd care a little bit.
我认为不是你的问题，这里太变态了
You know, I don't think it's you. This is a freaky place.
嘿，伙计们!
Hey, guys!
噢，不，是你的原因 -好吧
- Oh, no, it's you. - Yeah.
哦，这真的是太可怕了
Oh, this is terrible.
所有的东西都毁了
Everything is destroyed.
你看这个
Look at this.
它一定很重要我才会保存它 现在我看不出来它是什么东西
It meant enough for me to save, and now I can't tell what it is.
它还是软软的
It's still soft.
你觉得它是什么呢?
What do you think this is?
我想它是老鼠
I think it was a mouse.
-你还好吗? 甜心 -你觉得呢?
- How are you, honey? - How do you think I am?
你毁了我的童年回忆…
You've wrecked my childhood memories...
你们爱罗斯比爱我多
...you love Ross more than me.
我刚刚还拿死了的老鼠碰我的脸
And I just rubbed a dead mouse on my face.
甜心，我们爱你就像我们爱罗斯
Sweetheart, we love you just as much as Ross.
箱子的事我很抱歉…
I'm sorry about what happened...
也许我永远没办法补偿你…
...and I probably can't make it up to you...
但这是个开始
...but here's a start.
-这是什么? -我的保时捷钥匙
- What's this? - It's the key to my Porsche.
你的保时捷钥匙
Well, the key to your Porsche.
什么?
What?
What?!
我一直想把它卖掉 有天我在车子看到自己的倒影
I've considered getting rid of it. I saw my reflection the other day.
你妈说的对，我看起来像个蠢驴
Your mother's right, I do look like an ass.
你要把它送给我? 你一定是在开玩笑
You're giving it to me? You're kidding.
等一下
Well, wait a minute.
几箱蠢东西湿掉了，她就可以拿到保时捷?
A couple of stupid boxes get wet, and she gets a Porsche?
-我们去兜风吧 -太好了!
- Let's take a drive? - All right!
我呢? 我是医学奇迹!
What about me? I'm a medical marvel!
嘿，你们都在
Hey, guys.
你们看到钱德的椅子了吗?
Have you seen Chandler's chair?
乔伊把它弄坏了，于是他把它丢了
Joey broke it. He got rid of it.
你在开玩笑吗? 我得到了保时捷而且巴卡兰格被丢掉了
Are you kidding? I get a Porsche and the Barcalounger's gone?
这是有史以来最棒的一天
This is the best day ever!